

ABHINAV THORAT

AI/ ML ENGINEER

TCS Research & Innovation Labs

+91 950-345-8996

abhinavthorat@gmail.com

in Abhinav T.

@ abhinav.thorat@tcs.com

Pune, Maharashtra

AbhinavThorat

ABOUT

Domain: Machine Learning, Deep Learning & Artificial Intelligence.

Work area: Ad/Offer Optimization, Recommender System, Time Series Analysis, NLP.

Creator: Astromate | Instagram Domain: Astronomy, Astrophysics

Specializations

Python Tensorflow PyTorch

Libraries

Sci-kit Learn, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Scipy, Statsmodels, Plotly.

Tools & IDEs

Jupyter Notebook PyCharm SpyderIDE Atom

CERTIFICATION

Deep Learning Specialization (5 Course Specialization, Deeplearning.ai)

IBM Data Science Professional (10 Course Specialization, Coursera)

Machine Learning By Andrew Ng Stanford University

 $\label{eq:machine Learning A-ZTM: Hands-On Python \& R In Data Science - Udemy$

Complete Tensorflow 2 and Keras Deep Learning Bootcamp - Udemy

Python for Time Series Data Analysis - Udemy

WORK EXPERIENCES

Deep Learning Engineer

Investment Intelligence | April 2022 - Present

- Developing Deep Learning model for Marketing campaign strategies.
- Developing Attribution-based modeling for marketing Temporal Sequences.
- Developing models for marketing domain for Ad/Offer optimization and Budget Optimization.

Machine Learning Engineer

Liquid Intelligent Technologies | November 2019 - April 2021

- Developing Time series analysis and forecasting. with RNN.
- Developing recommender systems.
- Evaluating and implementing ML models based on Exploratory Data Analysis.

EDUCATION

Padmashree Dr D. Y. Patil Vidyapeeth

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electronics and Communications Engineering 2014-2018, CGPA:7.1

RLT College Of Science

HSC - Computer Science 2012-2014, CGPA:8.2